Call Me Lucky is a comedy, documentary film directed by Bobcat Goldthwait.
An inspiring, triumphant and wickedly funny portrait of one of comedy’s most enigmatic and important figures, CALL ME LUCKY tells the story of Barry Crimmins, a
beer-swilling, politically outspoken and whip-smart comic whose efforts in the 70s and 80s fostered the talents of the next generation of standup comedians.
But beneath Crimmins’ gruff, hard-drinking, curmudgeonly persona lay an undercurrent of rage stemming from his long-suppressed and horrific
abuse as a child – a rage that eventually found its way out of the comedy clubs and television shows and into the political arena.
Self, played by Barry Crimmins.
Self, played by David Cross.
Self, played by Patton Oswalt.
Self, played by Tom Kenny.
Self, played by Margaret Cho.
Self, played by Steven Wright.
Call Me Lucky is a 2015 American documentary film directed by Bobcat Goldthwait
about the life of satirist, author, and performer Barry Crimmins.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting.